investmentyogi.com 2017-06-24

# InvestmentYogi Privacy Policy -

#### Privacy Policy

Effective Date: January 1, 2009

At InvestmentYogi, we respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal information. Our privacy policy detailed below explains what information we may gather from your visit to our web sites and how such information may be used.

 **1\. How do we use information?**

We use the information that you provide to us when you register on a page on this site, fill out a survey, or otherwise voluntarily tell us about yourself or your activities, for our own use to improve our products and services and the content of this site. In addition we may use the information you provide us to send you marketing information about InvestmentYogi products and services.

 **2\. Third party providers**

We provide links to third party sites. As we do not control these web sites, InvestmentYogi is not responsible for the privacy practices of those web sites or the reliability of the information presented by such site. We therefore encourage you to review the policies posted on these and all third party sites.

 **3\. Profile and/or Registration Information**

The information and preferences you provide during registration is used for presenting and improving content and services that may be applicable to you. We may share this information with our partners only if you indicate interest in products that are serviced through our partners and their related concerns. We may use demographic and profile data for statistical analysis.

 **4\. Cookies**

InvestmentYogi uses browser-based cookies mainly for the purpose of identifying you on subsequent visits to our web sites. Occassionally, information from cookies may be used to tailor services that may better suit you. Please note that should you disable your browser from accepting cookies, some information or services may not be able to you.

 **5\. Security**

Protecting your personal information is important to us. We will take all reasonable technical measures to prevent loss or unintended use of your information. While we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warranty the security of information you send to us and you do so at your own risk.

 **6\. Privacy Policy Updates**

As we add more features and services to help you make better financial decisions, we update our privacy policies from time to time. Please visit this page often to review latest information on privacy practices at InvestmentYogi.
